FULL STACK DEVELOPER

# CONTACT

- in in/raul-lc/
- contact@ralo.dev
- Oaxaca, México
- <u>ralo.dev</u>

### **SUMMARY**

I'm a Full Stack Developer with more than 1 year of experience in web development. I'm adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions and determining customer satisfaction. Passionate programmer with drive to learn and master new technologies.

# LANGUAGES

# Spanish Native English C1 (TOEFL Certified)

## **SKILLS & TOOLS**

#### **Backend**

- Java
- TypeScript
- Spring Boot
- Nestis
- MySQL, PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- Supabase, Firebase
- Strapi

#### **Frontend**

- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Tailwind
- JQuery
- Vue.is
- React

# WORKING EXPERIENCE

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Technologial Institute of Oaxaca

JAN 2024 - PRESENT

I'm contributing to the development of an institutional system using Nestjs and TypeScript

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER INTERNSHIP**

Technologial Institute of Oaxaca MAY 2022 - JUL 2023

I was responsible for the development of a web application for the management of the institution's HR

department.

- Optimized report generation times by 90%
- Developed a fully functional HRMS using Spring Boot and Vue.js
- Successfully deployed and mantained the HRMS hosted at <a href="https://itoaxaca.tech">https://itoaxaca.tech</a>

# **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SYSTEMS ENGINEERING

2018 - 2023

National Technological Institute of Mexico

Check out my portfolio

